<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>delvinnicholas</title><link>https://delvinnicholas.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on delvinnicholas</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© {year}</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 21:17:25 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://delvinnicholas.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Advent of Cyber 2021 - Day 1 &amp; 2</title><link>https://delvinnicholas.github.io/blog/aocday1/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 21:17:25 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://delvinnicholas.github.io/blog/aocday1/</guid><description>Day 1 - Save The Gifts
IDOR Vulnerability Question :
After finding Santa&amp;rsquo;s account, what is their position in the company? Dengan mengubah parameter ID, kita dapat mengakses data milik orang lain. The Boss After finding McStocker&amp;rsquo;s account, what is their position in the company? Build manager After finding the account responsible for tampering, what is their position in the company?
Mischief Manager What is the received flag when McSkidy fixes the Inventory Management System?</description></item><item><title>Arkavidia7.0</title><link>https://delvinnicholas.github.io/blog/arkav7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2021 23:45:25 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://delvinnicholas.github.io/blog/arkav7/</guid><description>Tim Bo3d1 Kristian Anwar Delvin Nicholas Pada lomba ini, saya berkesempatan mengerjakan soal OSINT-1 dan Sad and Lonely, sedangkan Kristian mengerjakan soal KawaiiMetal.
OSINT-1
Deskripsi soal : Pada tanggal 9 Agustus 2019, sebuah artikel ilmiah dipublikasikan pada jurnal Computing and Software for Big Science. Salah satu penulis dari artikel ilmiah tersebut pernah menjadi narasumber pada suatu podcast. Sekitar tiga bulan setelah artikel tersebut dipublikasikan (1 Nov 2019), penulis ini mengunjungi suatu tempat di belahan bumi selatan.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://delvinnicholas.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://delvinnicholas.github.io/about/</guid><description>Welcome to my portfolio Profile My name is Delvin Nicholas, a junior year cyber security student from Binus University. I have a passion in photography, front-end and cyber security, especially in OSINT field.
Skills Photography and Videography Photo and Video Editing Basic Web Programming Penetration Testing Organizational Experience 2019 - 2020 : Staff of Keluarga Mahasiswa Katolik Binus University
2020 - 2021 : Staff of Cyber Security Community Binus University</description></item></channel></rss>